本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》 前情提要
Previously on 24
哈桑在伊斯兰共和国的卫队
Hassan's security forces in the Islamic Republic
正横扫首都  逮捕反对派领导人
are sweeping through the capital, arresting opposition leaders.
他若继续一意孤行  会威胁和平公约的合法性
And if he continues, it may delegitimize the peace accord.
总统阁下  如果你违背自己的人权宣言
I can't vouch for you as a reformer, Mr. President,
我是不能为你担保的
if you renege on your human rights obligations.
我兄弟想置我于死地
My brother tried to kill me,
而帮凶竟然是我自己的手下
helped by elements within my own government.
很明显  刺杀哈桑总统
Apparently, killing President Hassan
只是他弟弟计划的一部分
was only part of his brother's plan.
反恐小组已确定  他还试图弄到武器级的铀
CTU now believes he's also trying to acquire weapons-grade uranium.
什么时候给我浓缩铀棒
When can I take possession of the rods?
钱一到就给你
As soon as we have the money.
我找到了一个能治疗他的医生
I found a doctor who can treat him.
不找医生
No doctors.
当局知道核原料的事情
The authorities know about the nuclear material.
把欧力格送医会引狼入室
Putting Oleg in a clinic would lead them right to us.
莱文医生
Dr. Levine.
你们是怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
我弟弟病了
My brother is sick.
我帮你叫救护车
I'm gonna call you an ambulance.
不能让别人知道
No one can know about this.
不  别这样
No, no.
你到底想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
你是反恐小组的数据分析师
You're a data analyst for CTU.
你有渠道可以搞到很多好东西
You got access to all sorts of good stuff.
但都是有限制的
Yeah, but not unrestricted access.
必须得值至少六位数
Payout's got to be at least six figures.
你在俄罗斯黑帮中做了近两年的卧底
You were undercover for nearly two years with the Russian Mob.
你的意思是让我打回内部去吗
You're asking me to go back in?
瓦德米尔对她极其痴情  以至举止粗暴
Vladimir Laitanan was completely obsessed with her. It turned violent.
他有强奸她吗
Did he rape her?
看起来他至少曾几次试图强奸她
It looks like he tried a couple of times.
那现在我们能谈谈这笔买卖了吗
Can we talk about this deal now?
我也希望是这么简单
I wish it were that simple.
-把她绑起来  -什么
- Tie her up. - What?
你犯了个大错  这是笔千载难逢的买卖
Look, you're making a mistake. This is the chance of lifetime.
任务已经结束了
This operation's over.
瓦德米尔没上钩
Vladimir didn't take the bait.
蕾妮  我是杰克
Renee, it's Jack.
我知道你听得见  我现在就赶过来
I know you can hear me. I'm on my way now.
你不想做这笔买卖
You don't want to do this deal,
那就杀了我好了
then you might as well just kill me,
因为这笔买卖是我仅有的东西
because this deal is the only thing that I have.
开枪啊
Do it!
Pull the trigger!
我只是需要确定一下
I had to be sure.
杰克  你在吗
Jack, are you there?
怎么了
What's going on?
她混进去了
She's in.
他们相信她了
They bought her cover.
以下事件发生在晚上九点到十点
The following takes place between 9:00 P.M. and 10:00 P.M.
蕾妮  我看到你了
Renee, I've got a visual on you.
我关闭一会通讯器
I'm going off comm for a minute.
没事吧
You all right?
我是反恐小组  奥布赖恩
CTU, O'Brian.
克罗伊  我是杰克
Chloe, it's Jack.
你监听下蕾妮的通讯器  我要和黑斯廷斯谈
I want you to monitor Renee's comm. I need to speak to Hastings.
好  我帮你接进去
Okay, I'll put you through.
我在  杰克  请讲
I'm here, Jack. Go ahead.
我们要尽快把蕾妮·沃克撤出这次任务
We need to pull Renee Walker out now.
为什么
Based on what?
因为她会使自己和这次任务陷入险境
Because she's a danger to herself and this mission.
十分钟之前  勒塔纳威胁要处死她
Ten minutes ago, Laitanan threatened to execute her,
她说她早就活腻了
and she said she was sick of living
就想一死  她是当真的
and wanted to die and she meant it.
她肯定是给他下套呢
She must've been playing him.
不  她根本不在乎自己的死活
No. She doesn't care what happens to her,
这就让她变得极其危险
that's what makes her dangerous.
她就像一个定时炸弹
She's like a bomb ready to go off.
我们要在出事前救她出来
We need to get her out of there before that happens.
我理解你的心情  但在找到浓缩铀棒之前
Look, I understand your concern, but we can't just roll up this operation
不能随随便便结束这次行动
before we find those nuclear rods.
我们可以逮捕勒塔纳
We can arrest Laitanan.
如果他知道浓缩铀棒在哪里
If he knows how to find the rods,
我肯定能撬开他的嘴
I will make him talk.
如果我没猜错你的言下之意的话
If you're saying what I think you are,
我们不再干你那勾当了
we don't do that anymore.
那就做你们擅长的事好了
Then you people do what you do well-
可以给他豁免权什么的
offer him immunity or something.
这是俄罗斯犯罪集团
This is the Russian Syndicate.
他们行事极其谨慎  很会保护自己
They're very secretive, they protect their own.
勒塔纳不大可能会合作的
It is highly unlikely that Laitanan would cooperate.
那你最好再想个办法出来
Then you better find another way,
我不会因为反恐小组的失职
because I am not gonna let Renee die
而让蕾妮白白送命的
because CTU did their job badly.
绝对不会  你听明白了吗
I will not let that happen. Do you understand me?
杰克  如果你有其他的主意  我洗耳恭听
Jack, if you can think of something, I will listen.
但是现在
But right now,
蕾妮是我们化解危机的唯一希望
Renee's the only hope we have of neutralizing this threat.
我的命令是  让她继续卧底
And on my order, she stays in play.
杰克
Jack?
我扮成买家进去时会想办法把她救出来
I'll find a way to get her out when I go in as the buyer.
我会继续扮演她需要的角色
I'll stay under her place.
这样可以吗
Do we have a deal?
只要不影响这次任务的进程就可以
As long as you can do it without risking the mission.
我向你保证不会的
I give you my word.
奥迪斯探员和战术小队会和你在集结待命区会合
Agent Ortiz will meet you at the staging area with a TAC team.
他有你卧底所需要的一切资料
He'll have everything you need for your cover.
稍等  他们要走了
Hold on. They're moving.
我要重新打开通讯器了
I need to get back on comm.
我们先回店里
We'll go back to my shop,
再谈你介绍的买家
and we will discuss this buyer of yours.
丹娜
Dana...
开始给汉密尔顿堡的核突发事件组
start forwarding mission status reports
作行动状况的实时汇报
to the Nuclear Emergency Team at Fort Hamilton.
让他们准备好  一找到浓缩铀棒立刻行动
I want them ready to go in as soon as we find these nuclear rods.
我马上办  长官
I'm on it, sir.
翻译：aiai    wdjmhs    lemony    hodala    淑珍    ETSChina
■
时间轴：何何    泡泡龙    钉子      校对：何何    aiai
后期：冰河     监制：何何
■
喂
Yeah.
是我
It's me.
我有主意了
I've got something.
你速度还真快啊
Damn, you're fast.
稍等
Okay, hold on.
我们听听看
Let's hear it.
是纽约警局的证据保留室
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
清单显示
According to the manifest,
当地扫黄缉毒科刚截获了一批贩毒赃款
a local vice group just impounded a stash of drug money.
会在证据室保留48小时
It'll be held there for the next 48 hours.
多少钱
How much?
十二万
$120,000.
好  有何计划
All right, what's the plan?
你进去取出来
You go in and take it.
你什么意思  抢劫警察局吗
What do you mean, break into a police station?
你疯了吗
What, are you out of your mind?
那不是警察局  只是一个仓库而已
It's not a police station. It's a warehouse.
基本都是自动警报系统
Most of the security is automated.
我在这就可以加以操控
I can manipulate it from here.
你进去  拿钱走人
You walk in, you walk out with the cash.
我会一步步指导你该怎么做的
I'll talk you through it.
我拿到他们的密码之后
I need to access their security codes,
做一张钥匙卡帮你进入仓库
work up a keycard to get you inside the warehouse.
多久
How long?
三十分钟后在反恐小组门口等我
Meet me outside CTU in 30 minutes.
处理好你的紧急情况了吗
Did you take care of your situation?
什么情况
Situation?
那个让你不得不离开工作的大秘密
The big mystery you had to leave work for.
对  现在没事了
Oh, yeah, it's fine.
有事吗  阿洛
What do you need, Arlo?
我的无人机的防抱死制动系统有5%的滞后
I'm getting five percent lag in my Drone's ABS controls.
我的主机超负荷运转  处理器都开始发烫了
With everything going on, I think I'm just running hot.
我会在辅助服务器上多给你分些内存空间
Okay, I'll make sure to free up some memory space on the auxiliary servers.
多谢
Thanks.
要是有什么事情困扰你的话
You know, if there's something bothering you,
你可以趴在我肩膀上哭
you've always got my shoulder to cry on.
或是靠在其他身体部位哭也可以
Or any other body part.
我记住了
I will keep that in mind.
不过现在你最好集中精力
But, for now, why don't you focus on
为沃克和鲍尔提供空中监控支持
running aerial support for Walker and Bauer?
好吧
Okay.
卢戈  你歇会儿吧
Lugo, take a break.
我想跟她单独谈谈
I want to talk to her alone.
好吧  你引起我的兴趣了
All right, you have my attention.
说说你这个买主的来头
Tell me about this buyer.
他叫恩斯特·迈尔  德国军火商
His name's Ernst Meier. German arms dealer.
没听说过这个人
Never heard of him.
他主要在亚洲做生意
He does most of his business in Asia;
最近才到北美来开拓市场
he just started branching out into North America.
他想买什么货呢
What's he looking to buy?
武器级别的铀
Weapons-grade uranium.
你是认真的吗
You're serious.
很认真
Very.
俄罗斯犯罪集团从乌克兰走私了一批浓缩铀棒
Someone in the Russian Syndicate smuggled nuclear fuel rods out of the Ukraine.
他们打算在黑市上公开销售
They're planning on selling them on the open market.
我... 我不知道你在说什么
I... I have no idea what you're talking about.
真的  蕾妮
I don't, Renee.
但你可以找到渠道  你手眼通天
But you can find out. You're very well connected.
我向来赞赏你的野心
I have always admired your ambition,
但是你在跟魔鬼打交道
but you're chasing the devil.
买卖AK-47  不会有人在意
Dealing AK-47s- no one really cares.
但核原料的话...
But nuclear material?
丰厚回报之下必有勇夫
But the profit is worth it.
你缺钱吗
You need money, huh?
那你随时可以为我工作
You can always come work for me.
不  这笔买卖可以令我不用再为任何人工作了
No, I'm doing this so I don't ever have to work for anyone.
请坐
Have a seat.
如果我帮你找到渠道的话
If I could find out...
我能得到多少提成
...what would it be worth?
总额的30%
30% of the deal.
这笔钱你这一辈子都花不完
that is more money than you could possibly know what to do with.
迈尔说这些浓缩铀很快就要被别人买走了
Look, Meier says these rods are going to be sold soon,
所以  如果你想参与竞价的话
so if we want to make a counter bid,
就需要尽快行动
it has to happen fast.
如果你不想参与的话就告诉我  我去找别人
If you don't know anything, tell me, so I can go somewhere else.
你跟这个人熟吗  信任他吗
How well do you know this man? You trust him?
他是我最信任的人  我跟他一起两年了
There's no one I trust more. I've been with him for two years.
"一起"是什么意思
What do you mean "With"?
生意上的关系
It's professional.
你到底能不能帮我们
Can you help us or not?
我去打几个电话
I'll make a few calls,
摸一摸情况
see what I can find out.
不过呢
But, uh,
我得跟这个迈尔聊一聊
I'm going to have to meet this Meier.
-为了表示诚意  他要先交钱  -交多少
- And I need a good faith payment up front. - How much?
五百万
Five million.
这可是一大笔钱啊  瓦德
That's a lot of money, Vlad.
听着  我打这些电话也是冒很大风险的
Look, I'm taking big risk just making these calls.
况且  五百万同你的买主用来买浓缩铀的
Besides, 5 million is nothing compared to what your buyer
全款相比简直是九牛一毛
will have to pay for nuclear fuel rods.
好吧
Fine.
我去问问他  但是我不能给你打包票
I'll ask him, but I can't make any promises.
他要我帮他的话  就要付这笔入伙费
If he wants my help, that's the price of admission.
好吧
Okay.
第12街和市场街拐角有一间车库
There's a parking garage on the corner of 12th and Market Street.
有人会在那车库的屋顶上同他见面
Someone will meet him there, on the roof.
一旦钱划到我们的账户上
Once the money is in our account,
就把他带过来  我们再谈
they'll bring him back here, we will talk.
我给他打电话
I'll give him a call.
见到你很高兴
It's good to see you.
你又要开始让我辗转难眠了
You're going to make me start losing sleep again.
我会把迈尔的口信捎给你的
I'll let you know what Meier says.
我去叫我的人准备
I'll tell my men.
你们单独聊吧
I'll give you privacy for your call.
杰克  你在听吗
Jack, were you listening?
嗯  我们准备把钱转到他的账户上
Yeah, we're ready to wire the money to his account.
你什么时候能到那里
When can you be there?
我准备好伪装之后马上过去
As soon as I finish prepping my cover.
我距离集合待命区已经很近了
I'm almost at the staging area.
最多三十分钟
30 minutes tops.
你那里情况如何
How you holding up?
跟禽兽同处一室真的很难熬
It's hard to be in the same room with this son of a bitch.
我能搞定
I can handle it.
我会尽快赶到的
I'll be there as soon as I can.
好的
Okay.
吗啡很快就会起作用了
Morphine will take effect in just a few moments.
别担心  欧力格
Don't worry, Oleg.
你会好起来的
You're going to be fine.
也许... 你告诉我你兄弟身上到底
It, uh... it might help me if I knew
发生了什么会对我诊断大有帮助
exactly what happened to your brother.
他怎么会受到武器级别铀的放射污染
How did he get exposed to weapons-grade uranium?
不用你操心  你只需要确保他能活命
Don't worry about that. Just make sure he lives.
又是他打来的  对吗
It's him again, isn't it?
这是他第二次打来电话了  你应该接听
The second time he's called. You should answer it.
喂
Hello?
你怎么不接电话呢
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
我打了两次了
I called you twice.
可能过隧道时没了信号
Must have been in the tunnel.
乌兰娜说你们还没到别墅那里
Ulana says you're not at the house yet.
-你们在哪  -堵车了
- Where are you? - Stuck in traffic.
跟她说还要再等一会儿
Tell her it's going to be a while.
欧力格怎么样了
How's Oleg?
他没事  睡觉呢
He's okay. Sleeping.
到了别墅后马上给我打电话
Let me know when you get to the house.
好的
I will.
是他  对吗
It was him, wasn't it?
别担心  好吗
Don't worry, okay?
当他发现时你已经好了
By the time he finds out, you'll already have been treated.
那就没问题了
Then it won't matter.
只是你弟弟的检查结果到了
Hey, it's just your brother's test results.
你要是敢跟我耍小聪明的话
You say or do anything that I don't like,
我的人就会宰了你老婆和女儿
and my men will kill your wife and daughter.
开门去
Open the door.
您要的血常规化验  医生
The blood work you ordered, Doctor.
谢谢
Thank you.
我发现这里没有病人姓名
Uh, I noticed there was no patient name.
对  你说得对
Uh, yeah, you're right.
-我忘记填了  -那我帮您填上
- I forgot to put that down. - Oh, well, I can do it for you.
不用  我待会自己填
No, I'll take care of it later.
你还好吗  医生
Is everything okay, Doctor?
我很好
Fine.
只是工作得比我预计的晚了一些
I'm just working a little later than I expected.
那好吧
Okay.
表现不错
You did good.
结果如何
What does it say?
你兄弟受到了至少四百雷姆的放射污染
Your brother has been exposed to at least 400 rems,
放射物的化学毒性导致了肾衰竭
and the chemical toxicity of the radiation is causing renal failure.
我知道情况严重
I know it's serious.
你到底能不能治好他
Can you help him or not?
他得进行骨髓移植
He needs a bone marrow transplant.
需要一个设备齐全的六人外科手术小组
That requires a six-man surgical team in a fully equipped facility.
此时此地  你总能做些什么
There has to be something you can do right here, right now.
我可以给他开些能有助于排出放射物
There are some drugs I could give him that will help flush out the radiation
并促进白细胞修复的药物
and stimulate white blood cell repair,
这只是权宜之计  我不能保证他会康复
but that's a half measure. I can't guarantee he'll recover.
我弟弟不会死
My brother is not going to die.
他的命掌握在你的手里  医生
It's up to you, Doctor.
快去
Now get to work.
好  明白
Okay, got it.
反恐小组打来电话
That was CTU.
你的海外账户准备完毕
Your offshore account's in place.
他们正在把汇钱方法发送到你的掌上电脑上
They're forwarding instructions to your PDA on how to wire the money.
借过
Excuse me.
我跟黑斯廷斯谈过了
I spoke with Hastings.
他说一旦你接上头
He said, as soon as you're under
确定勒塔纳能帮我们找到浓缩铀棒
and we have confirmation that Laitanan can get us to the nuclear rods,
我们就马上把蕾妮·沃克救出来
we're pulling Renee Walker out.
没错
That's right.
怎么了  杰克
What's going on, Jack?
黑斯廷斯说她情绪不稳定
Hastings said something about her being unstable.
我没时间解释
I don't have time to explain it.
听我指挥就行
Just follow my lead.
不暴露身份的话怎么继续行动
How do you want to work this without breaking cover?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
好吧  有两个飞车射击队协调作战
All right. Well, I got two teams running coordinated drive-bys.
当她完成使命时  他们随时准备营救她出来
They'll be ready to extract her when she's clear.
不行  这是他们的地盘
No. These guys own this neighborhood.
肯定到处都有眼线
They'll have eyes everywhere.
你的人很可能被发现
Your men will run the risk of being spotted.
我是老江湖了  杰克
I've done this before, Jack.
我在费卢杰执行过类似的行动
I ran an operation just like it in Fallujah.
但我是指挥官  按我的命令行事
And I'm in command. You're going to do exactly what I tell you.
杰克  做好准备
Jack, stand by.
勒塔纳回来了
Laitanan's back.
我得去监听  失陪了
I need to listen to this. Excuse me.
我和手下打过招呼了
I spoke to my men.
你和买家通过电话了吗
Did you get your buyer on the phone?
他同意预付这笔钱
He agreed to the money.
-二十分钟内到停车场  -很好
- He'll be at the parking garage in 20 minutes. - Very good.
那我们还有点时间叙叙旧
We have a little time to catch up.
还喜欢喝单一纯麦威士忌吗
Do you still like your single malts?
现在不想喝
Uh, not right now.
确定吗  这可是三十年陈的酒啊
You sure? It's a 30 year.
不用  谢谢
No, thanks.
刚在河边你说什么来着
What you said earlier... down at the river...
你厌倦了生活  就想一死
you were tired of living, wanted to die.
发生了什么事
What happened to you?
这不重要
It's not important.
对我来说重要
It is to me.
不用担心
Look, you don't have to worry about it.
只要交易完成  其他的都将不再重要了
Once I make this deal, none of it will matter.
过去那几年  受罪的不止是你一个人
Well, you're not the only one who's been suffering these past few years.
虽然难以启齿
It's hard for me to admit,
但是  我从未原谅自己对你的所作所为
but, uh... I never forgave myself for what I did to you.
过去的都过去了  忘了吧
It's in the past. Forget it.
我不想忘记
I don't want to forget it.
那晚我喝得太多了  意识不清醒
I had too much to drink that night, i wasn't thinking clearly.
从来没见你道过歉  史无前例啊
Never heard you apologize for anything. It's definitely a first.
我只是想纠正过去的错误
Look, I'm just trying to make things right.
你用不着这么得理不饶人吧
You don't have to be such a bitch about it.
我得理不饶人了吗  也许我应该道歉
Was I being a bitch? Maybe I should apologize.
真是巾帼不让须眉  你从不低头  是不是
Oh, you're something else. You never back down, do you?
我想念我们斗嘴的样子
I've missed our little arguments.
靠近我你还是会紧张
You're still nervous around me.
我不该大惊小怪
I shouldn't be surprised.
不是因为你
It's not you.
那是因为别人吗
Someone else?
不是
No.
那是怎么回事
What is it, then?
听着  我只是...
Look, I'm just...
我只是担心这次交易  那么多钱都悬着呢
I'm just nervous about the deal. Could be a lot of money at stake.
如果你愿意  你得到的不仅仅是钱
There's more for you here than just money, if you want it.
听着
Look...
我来不是为了这个
I didn't come here for this.
是吗  你有那么多人可以选
Really. All the people you could've gone to,
可你偏偏挑了我
you knocked on my door.
因为你人脉广
Because you're connected.
-就因为这个吗  -对
- That's the only reason? - Yes.
我不信
I don't believe you.
那是你的事
That's your problem.
管好你的舌头
You should watch your tongue.
否则不定哪天就没了
You might lose it one day.
你刚说我可以去冲个澡
Uh... you said that I could get cleaned up.
是的
Yeah.
洗手间里有淋浴
Bathroom has a shower.
谢谢
Thank you.
奥迪斯探员  立刻行动
Agent Ortiz, we need to move now.
蕾妮给她的买家打过电话了
Renee called her buyer.
他同意预先支付五百万
He agreed to pay the $5 million up front.
你去会会他  带几个弟兄过去
I want you to meet with him. Take a couple men.
瓦德  做核武器买卖是个错误
This is a mistake, Vlad. Getting involved in nuclear arms-
这不是钱多钱少的问题
it doesn't matter how much money is at stake.
我没打算做这个买卖
I have no intention of pursuing this deal.
什么意思
What do you mean?
跟买家接头后  钱一进账
When you've picked up the buyer, when the money has been transferred into our account,
就干掉他  把尸体扔到河里
you kill him, put him in the river,
钱我们自己留着
keep the money for ourselves.
蕾妮怎么办
What about Renee?
从今以后她就和我们一伙了
She'll be working with us from now on.
可杀了买家  她肯定不乐意
We are going to kill her buyer. She's not going to be happy about that.
你没听到她的话吗  她已经一无所有了
You heard what she said. She's got nothing left.
无处可去  是一个绝望的女人了
Nowhere to go. Desperate woman.
我给了她活下去的理由
I give her reason to live.
懂了没
Okay?
交给我了
I'll take care of it.
哈桑总统的卫队
President Hassan's security forces...
仍在镇压反对派
they're still cracking down on the opposition,
并且没有任何停止的迹象
and they're not showing any signs of letting up.
恐怕哈桑总统对您的忠告置若罔闻了
I'm afraid your warning to President Hassan has fallen on deaf ears,
总统阁下
Madam President.
谁拍的视频
Who filmed this?
BBC的特约记者从一个目击者手里买的
Stringer for the BBC bought it from an eyewitness.
英国政府方面已经看过了
And they've already seen it on Downing Street.
所以伊桑想让你看看这个
That's why Ethan wanted you to see this now.
谣言四起
The rumors have already started
说是英国正打算拒绝签字同时退出和谈
that the British are pulling out as signatories to the accord.
那我得跟首相谈谈
Then I need to talk to the prime minister.
不仅是英国  总统阁下
It's not just the British, Madam President.
德国和埃及也纷纷表示要退出和谈
The Germans and Egyptians are also positioning themselves to pull out,
如果没有他们的支持
and if we lose their support...
和平会谈就胎死腹中了
The peace deal is dead.
如果让他们明白现在的事态
Maybe if they understood the circumstances
哈桑总统正努力阻止他弟弟获得核武器
that Hassan is trying to prevent his brother from acquiring a nuclear weapon.
恕我直言  总统阁下
With respect, Madam President,
如果这个消息散布出去了  势必会造成恐慌
sharing that intelligence with the delegates might spread a panic.
没错  但我还是需要争取一些时间
You're right, but I still need to buy some time.
召集各国代表
Assemble the representatives
让每个签署国都来出席会议
from every signatory country attending the conference.
我亲自去请求他们让和谈继续
I want to appeal to them myself to stay the course.
哈桑总统怎么办
What about President Hassan?
要邀请他吗
Shouldn't we include him?
还是先稳住其他代表的情绪吧
Not until I've taken the temperature of the other delegates.
我不想把他逼得太急了
I don't want to push him too hard.
这是什么
What is it?
按您的吩咐  这是被抓嫌犯们的背景资料
As you requested, these are backgrounds on all the detainees.
我们的卫队已对首都进行了初步搜捕
Our security police have completed their initial sweep of the capital city.
已有65名反对分子被捕
65 known members of the opposition have been arrested
正在对他们进行审问
and are being questioned.
有什么收获吗
Have you learned anything?
他们中有我弟弟的同党吗
Were any of them working with my brother?
现在还说不准
It's too early to tell.
怎么了  总统阁下
What's wrong, sir?
其中一名嫌犯...
One of the suspects...
是我国驻联合国代表团中一位代表的亲戚
has family connections to a member of my delegation here at the UN.
-谁  -贾莫特
- Who? - Jamot.
他们是表亲
They are cousins.
这不代表贾莫特和这次阴谋有瓜葛
That doesn't mean that Jamot is involved in any of this.
我们要确保万无一失
We need to make sure.
我们会调查他的通话记录和近期活动
We'll check his phone records and other recent activities
看是否有任何异常的地方
for any suspicious behavior.
很好  但我还是希望先拘留他
Good. But I also want him taken into custody.
-什么  -逮捕他
- Sir? - Arrest him.
带他到使馆接受审讯
Take him to our embassy for interrogation.
总统阁下  恕我直言
Mr. President, with respect,
贾莫特是您内阁核心中的信臣
Jamot is a trusted member of your inner circle.
现在指证他的证据还不足
The evidence against him is purely circumstantial.
我也曾一度信任我的弟弟
I trusted my brother as well.
您确定要这么做吗
Are you sure this is what you want?
他可是一名政府官员
He is a public official.
逮捕他会被人察觉的
It will not go unnoticed.
我不在乎
I don't care!
我才不在乎别人怎么想
I don't care what anyone thinks.
我今天九死一生
I was almost killed today.
你难道已经忘了
Or have you forgotten?
我当时和您在同一辆车里  总统阁下
I was in the car with you, sir.
那你应该知道怎么做了
Then you should know what needs to be done.
是的  总统阁下
Yes, sir.
钥匙卡激活完毕
Keycard Activation Completed
-把我忘了吗  -什么
- Forget about me? - What?
我叫阿洛·格拉斯
My name's Arlo Glass.
我是你反恐小组的同事
I'm one of your coworkers at CTU.
你刚说你要去为辅助服务器释放内存空间
You said you'd free up some memory space on the auxiliary servers.
我正要去做
I'm getting to it.
都什么时代了  我们有重任在身
In which century? We're in the middle of an operation
而我的空中监测画面却处于龟速运行
and my aerial feed is running in slow-motion.
我接下来就去搞定它  阿洛
It's next on my list, Arlo.
你要去哪
Where are you going now?
上厕所  满意了吗
To the bathroom. Is that okay with you?
奥布赖恩
Hey, O'Brian,
你注意到丹娜有点怪怪的吗
you notice anything weird about Dana?
那位完美小姐吗
Miss Perfect?
她看起来有点心不在焉
She seems distracted,
老是找借口离开岗位
always making excuses to leave.
可能她就是不想见到你
Maybe she's avoiding you.
什么
What?
如果有人整天色咪咪地看着我  我也会那么做
Well, that's what I would do if someone were drooling over me all day.
你该庆幸她没向人力资源部门打你的小报告
You're lucky she hasn't reported you to Human Resources.
如果你是在吃醋
If you weren't so jealous,
那我告诉你我是认真的
you'd see I was asking you a serious question.
哦  对  我吃醋了
Oh, yeah, I'm jealous.
拜托  请在我走开时窥视我的俏臀吧
Please, won't you stare at my ass as I walk away?
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
待在这
Stay here.
这里有证据保留室所在位置及其地形图
This has the address and schematic of the evidence lockup.
从东南面的入口进去
You'll go through the southeast entrance.
用这张钥匙卡通过安检
This keycard will get you access.
我们怎么才能找到钱
How do we find the money?
证据存储箱都有编号
The evidence bins are numbered.
赃款箱的编号为4301
You're looking for 4301.
这是个专用的通讯器
This is a dedicated comm unit.
是一种耳机  戴上就能听到我说话了
It's an earpiece; you'll be able to hear me.
必须严格按我说的做  你就能自由进出了
Do exactly what I tell you to do and you'll be in and out.
没人会知道你去过那里
No one will know you were there.
听着  事成后
Listen... I help you do this
就别再来烦我了
and you never call me again.
就这么定了  好吗
That's the deal, right?
当然  珍妮  就这么定了
Sure, Jen, that's the deal.
我们一到证据保留室就给你电话
I'll call you when we get to the lockup.
好的
Okay.
你真苗条
You look thin.
请你出去一下
Be out in a minute.
我可不想久等
I don't want to wait that long.
拜托  瓦德米尔  让我先穿上衣服
Vladimir, please, just let me get dressed.
何必要多此一举
Why waste the energy?
反正过一会我又要把你脱光
I'll just have to get you undressed all over again.
听着  我告诉过你我不是来干这个的
Look, I already told you I didn't come here for this.
你是说过  但见我也是你来的原因之一吧
That's what you say, but part of you came here to see me.
承认吧
Admit it.
没什么好承认的
There's nothing to admit.
为什么那么不愿意承认事实呢
Why is it so hard for you to admit the truth?
你和我一样饥渴
You want this just as much as I do.
我不会再说一次了
I'm not going to tell you again.
让我先穿上衣服再说
Leave me alone and let me get dressed.
过来
Come here.
我叫你过来
I said come here.
要么过来要么滚出去
Come here or get out.
我一个电话  这次交易就取消了
I call my men and the deal's off.
我... 我想先喝一杯
I'll, um... I'll take that drink now.
先把身子擦干
Dry yourself off.
准备好了就出来
Come out when you're ready.
蕾妮  听到了吗
Renee, do you copy?
是的  杰克
Yeah, Jack.
你没必要那么做
You don't have to do this.
我已经让一个小队待命了
I've got a team standing by.
我们现在就能把你救出来
We can get you out of there now.
那我们岂不是一筹莫展了
Where would that leave us?
我得继续潜伏下去
I've got to stay under.
我们再想其他办法
We'll find another way.
没其他办法了
There is no other way.
蕾妮  别那么做
Renee, don't do this.
蕾妮
Renee...
去见瓦德的人吧
Go meet Vlad's men.
等你到这了  我会去见你
I'll see you when you get here.
你为什么不听我的劝
Why won't you listen to me?
我要关通讯器了
I'm going dark.
蕾妮  等...
Renee, wai...
这一系列拘捕给我国政府继续支持和平协议
These arrests are making it very difficult for my government to continue
造成了很大的阻碍
to support the peace agreement.
至于哈桑总统
President Hassan
很难忽视他的所作所为引起的反响
can't ignore the repercussions of what he's doing.
我了解哈桑总统
I know President Hassan.
他是个理性的人  是个好人
He is a rational man, a good man.
这些行为一定是事出有因
There must be a reason for these actions,
我说这话  不仅是作为他的代表
and I'm not just speaking as his delegate
也是作为他的朋友说的
but as his friend.
作为他的朋友  你该让他知道
Well, as his friend, you need to let him know
不止我国政府怀有极大的忧虑
that my government is not the only one with grave concerns.
这次会谈正面临着分崩离析的危险
This conference is at risk of falling apart...
抱歉  打扰一下
Excuse me, I'm sorry to interrupt.
贾莫特先生  能和您私下说句话吗
Mr. Jamot, may I speak with you privately?
是的  当然可以
Yes, of course.
失陪了
Excuse me.
没关系
Of course.
怎么了
What is it?
我接到命令  带您去大使馆回答些问题
I've been ordered to escort you to the embassy to answer some questions.
什么问题
Regarding?
国内治安问题
An internal security matter.
请跟我们走一趟
Please come with us.
我想要知道  这是怎么回事
Well, I-I would like to know what this is about.
到了大使馆我们会解释一切的  先生
We'll explain everything to you at the embassy, sir.
那就得过一阵了
Well, it will have to wait.
我正准备开个会
I am about to go into a meeting.
这事不能耽搁  先生
It cannot wait, sir.
我们现在就得动身
We need to go right now.
你这是想拘捕我吗
Are you arresting me?
我觉得慎重一些方为上策
It would be best if we kept this discreet.
这太过分了
This is outrageous.
我要和哈桑总统谈谈
I demand to speak with President Hassan.
就是哈桑总统下的命令
President Hassan is the one who gave this order.
我不会再客气地请你了
I will not ask you again.
跟我们走一趟吧
Come with us.
很好
Very well.
带他上车
Take him to the car.
我马上就过去
I'll be right there.
没事吧
Is everything all right?
一切正常  阁下
Everything is fine, sir.
失陪了
Please excuse me.
喂
Hello.
-是我  你身边没人吧  -没人
- It's me. Are you alone? - Yes.
怎么了  听起来你很不安
What's wrong? You sound upset.
我不希望你也背上包袱
I didn't want to burden you with this,
但我得和你谈谈你父亲的事
but I need to speak with you about your father.
怎么了
What is it?
我现在要去大使馆
I have to go to the embassy right now.
等我回来再私下见你
I'll meet you in private when I get back.
你每天要给他注射两次长春地辛
You're going to give him vindesine twice daily,
早晚各一次
morning and night.
直接注射到输液包里
Inject it right into the I.V. Bag,
就像我现在这样
just like I'm doing.
你得小心点
You're going to want to be careful.
辐射中毒是会通过体液传播的
Radiation poisoning is transferable through bodily fluids.
你在听吗
Are you paying attention?
是  我知道了
Yes, I see.
他每隔一天需要用顺铂
He's also going to get cisplatin every other day,
但可以口服
but he can take that in pill form.
我先给你三周的量
I'm going to give you three weeks' worth.
我怎么能看出来他好转了没有
How will I know if he's getting better?
如果治疗有效
If the treatment's working,
在七到十天内  他的症状会逐渐消退
his symptoms will begin to subside in seven to ten days.
我们很快就要走了
We're going to be leaving soon.
-去哪  -去郊区别墅那里
- Where? - To the country house.
医生给了我治疗你的所有药物
The doctor's giving me everything I need to treat you.
你会好起来的  欧力格
You're going to get better, Oleg.
是护士带剩下的药物来了
That's the nurse with the rest of the medicine.
把武器放下  约瑟夫
Throw down your weapon, Josef.
照我说的做
Do what I said.
别自讨苦吃
Don't make this worse than it is.
放下枪
Drop it!
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
还有谁知道欧力格的病情
Who else knows about Oleg's sickness?
还有谁知道
Who else knows?
只有那个医生
Just the doctor.
确定吗
Are you sure?
确定
I'm sure.
拔掉他的输液管
Undo him.
等等  住手
Hey, wait, stop.
-你要干什么  -你爸派我们来带你们回家
- What are you doing? - Your father sent us to bring you home.
-现在就走  约瑟夫  -约瑟夫
- Now, Josef. - Josef...
没事的
It's okay.
照他说的做吧
Just do what he says.
我来扶他
I have him.
找到他们了
We found them.
他们在哪
Where were they?
弗农山的一间诊所
A clinic in Mount Vernon.
多少人知道欧力格的事
How many people found out about Oleg?
只有一个  一个医生
Only one... a doctor.
但我们已经摆平他了
but we've taken care of him.
没人知道我们来过
Nobody will know we were here.
很好
Good.
把我的儿子们带回来吧
Now, bring my sons to me.
了解
Da.
走吧
Let's go.
是迈尔吗
Meier?
没错
That's right.
你是德国来的
You are from Germany.
不莱梅
Bremen.
但我从小跟着我父亲旅行
But I grew up traveling with my father.
没去过  不过听说那里的女人很美
Never been there, but I hear the women are beautiful.
没错  可惜啊  我忙得没时间玩女人
You heard right. Unfortunately I am too busy working to enjoy them.
你有美国口音
You have American accent.
我在这上的大学
I went to university here,
而且和我做生意的人大多说英语
and most of the people I do business with speak English.
估计说话就变味了
I guess it rubs off.
我们也许该说英语  德语太...
Maybe we should speak English, German is such a...
肮脏了
Dirty language.
你也不是干净人
And you are dirty people.
不过既来之则安之
But here we are.
我们各取所需
We both need something from each other.
我们还要不要做交易了
Are we going to do business or not?
五百万美金在哪
Where is the $5 million?
我没和勒塔纳说上话之前你见不到一分钱
You don't see any money until I talk to Laitanan.
你有什么疑问的话
If you have questions,
问我吧
ask me.
我不想和你谈
I don't want to talk to you.
给他打电话  不然我就开车走人
Get him on the phone or I drive away.
现在就打
Now.
喂
Yes?
迈尔来了
Meier is here.
他说不先和你通话  就不会转账
He won't transfer the money until he speaks with you first.
把电话给他
Put him on.
我是迈尔
This is Meier.
是的  迈尔先生
Yes, Mr. Meier.
有什么问题吗
What's the problem?
在你收到钱之后
After you get your money,
还要多久我才能得到我要的消息
how long till I get my information?
不会很久  我只需要打几个电话
Not very long; I just have to make a few calls.
不会超过一个小时
No more than an hour.
蕾妮在哪
Where is Renee?
她很忙
She's busy.
我想和她谈谈
I would like to talk to her.
你来了就能见到她了
You can see her when you get here.
钱不到位
We have nothing more to discuss
我们就没什么好说的了
until the money's in place.
把电话给卢戈
Now, get Lugo on the phone.
好吧
Fine.
说吧
Go ahead.
一旦确定钱到帐
Once the money is confirmed into our account,
你知道该怎么处理
you know what to do.
知道
Yes.
我要你的帐号
I need your account number.
我正进行多账户转账
I'm transferring the money through multiple accounts
这样钱的来路就不会被追踪到  要花点时间
so it can't be traced. This will take a moment.
我们等着
We'll wait.
搞定了吗
Is it done?
还没
Not yet.
我的买家在钱方面的信誉不错  瓦德米尔
My partner's good for the money, Vladimir.
你该打电话找寻浓缩铀棒的下落了
You should be making calls, tracking down the rods.
我不会打电话的
I'm not going to make any calls,
因为我根本就没打算和你的买家做这笔买卖
'cause there isn't going to be any deal with your partner.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
一旦我们拿到钱
Once we have the money...
交易结束
it's over.
他就对我们毫无用处了
We don't need him anymore.
而我们就又多了五百万
And we'll be $5 million richer.
你这混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我可不会和贩卖核武器的人
I'm not about to get involved with the kind of people
搅合在一起
who traffic in nuclear arms.
瓦德米尔  听着  你不能这么做
Vladimir, listen, you can't do this.
怎么  这男人对你很重要吗
Why? This man mean something to you?
不是  我为了这桩买卖花了一年多时间
No, but I worked for more than a year to make this deal.
我可不会因为你没这胆子做就轻易放手
I'm not just gonna let it go because you don't have the guts to see it through.
这和胆子大不大无关
Hey, this isn't about guts.
这是关于是否是明智之举的问题
This is about being smart.
真的是这样吗
Really?
难道一辈子做点小军火买卖就是明智的吗
Is it smart to keep selling small arms for the rest of your life?
我给你找来千载难逢的好机会
I bring you the score of a lifetime,
你就这样糟蹋了是吗
and you just piss it away?
就仅仅为了那五百万吗
For what- for $5 million?
那能够你挥霍多久呢
How long is that going to last you?
足够久了
Long enough.
你决不是一点小钱就能满足的主儿
You're more than all this.
我了解你
I know it.
所以我才找你来接这笔买卖
It's why I brought this deal to you.
我们能行的  一起大干一番
We can do this. Together.
一旦我们做成了这笔买卖就发财了
Once we've made the deal and we have the money,
我们就能在一起了
we can be together.
就可以重新开始了
We could start over.
不再受制于人了
Make our own moves.
所以我的买家还不能死
But I need my buyer. Alive.
抱歉
Sorry.
我意已决
This is the way I want it.
你以后会明白的  这是最明智的做法
You'll see. It's for the best.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
打电话
Making a call.
放下电话
Put down the phone.
我叫你放下电话
I said put it down!
永远不要和我对着干
Don't ever go against me!
事到如今你应该很明白这个道理了  蕾妮
Renee, you should know that by now.
听懂了吗
Okay?!
还有多久
How much longer?
马上就好了
It's almost done.
好了
There.
钱已到账
The money's in your account.
谢了  迈尔先生
Thank you, Mr. Meier.
放下武器  马上放下武器
Drop the weapon. Now! Drop it!
你真以为我能傻到一个人来交易吗
You really think I'm that stupid? That I'd come here alone?
给你的人打电话  快
Call your man. Do it!
电话给我
Give me the phone.
我看到了  钱已到帐
I see we have the money.
迈尔死了没
Is Meier dead?
还没  你的三个手下已经被我杀了
Not exactly, but I've just taken out three of your men,
现在准备杀第四个
and I'm ready to take out the fourth.
你真以为你可以黑吃黑  得到这五百万吗
You really think you can roll me for $5 million?
蕾妮在哪
Where's Renee?
她就在这  她没事
She's right here. She's fine.
我需要证明
I want proof now!
跟你的买家说句话
Say something to your partner.
迈尔  你还好吗
Meier, are you okay?
满意了吗
Satisfied?
蕾妮告诉我你准备将贵帮做大做强
Renee told me you were ready to take your organization to the next level.
很明显她看错人了
Apparently, she was wrong.
那也不一定  我很乐意重新考虑一下
Not necessarily. I'm willing to reconsider the situation.
你应该非常庆幸才对
The only thing you should consider yourself is lucky.
因为我现在仍然想做这笔买卖
And I still want this deal to happen.
否则你早就死了
Otherwise, you'd be dead.
如果你胆敢再耍花招  我们就开战了
You try something like this again, we're going to war,
那恐怕是你最不愿意看到的局面
and that's the last thing you want.
把电话给我的人
Let me talk to my man.
好吧
Fine.
喂
Yes?
把他带过来
Bring him back here.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
对
Yeah.
他想要和你会面
He wants to see you.
站起来
Get up.
你来开车
Move to the driver's-side door.
慢慢地走过去
Slowly.
上车
Get in.
我很抱歉  欧力格
I'm sorry, Oleg.
我不能眼睁睁看着他死
I couldn't let him die.
他可是我弟弟啊
He's my brother.
他还是我儿子呢
And he's my son.
你觉得他这样我心里好受吗
Do you think this is any easier for me?
他本来可以好起来的
It would've worked.
医生已经在治疗他了
The doctor was treating him.
你违抗了我的命令  约瑟夫
You disobeyed me, Josef.
你让整个家族的安危命悬一线
You put this family at risk.
当您派人去诊所的时候
You put this family at risk
才是让整个家族命悬一线
when you sent those men into the clinic.
他们杀了三个人
They killed three people!
如果警察开始着手调查怎么办
What do you think's gonna happen when the police start to investigate?!
你翅膀硬了  敢质疑老子的判断力了吗
Who are you to question my judgment?
你是长子
You are my first-born.
在所有人中你最应该尊敬我
You, of all people, should give me respect.
我一直很尊重您  但是这次您肯定错了
I do respect you. But this time you're wrong.
医生说可以治愈欧力格的
The doctor said that Oleg could be treated.
他都教我怎么做了
He showed me how!
我们只需要给他用药就行了
All we need is the medicine!
国有国法  帮有帮规  约瑟夫
There are rules, Josef.
规矩很简单
They are simple rules.
永远不要坏了规矩
And they must never be broken!
永远不威胁到家族的安危  永不
Never endanger the family; never.
永远不要违抗你父亲的命令
And never disobey an order from your father.
爸爸
Papa...
不要  求您了
No, please,
这是你逼我的  约瑟夫
You made me do this, Josef.
求您了  不要
Please. Please don't.
儿子  对不住了
I'm sorry, my son.
站起来
Get up.
起来
Get up!
现在给格雷戈神父打电话
Now, call Father Gregor.
他会为欧力格祷告的
He'll pray over Oleg.
他完成祷告以后  自会厚葬你弟弟
When he's finished, we'll bury your brother.
绝对不要再违抗我的命令
Never disobey me again.